Guide to the Werner Pfeiffer Collection, 1953-2017
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- 1000 MISCELLANEOUS
  - 1005: X-mas Cards
    - X-mas Card no. 15, 1988; (5 x 7) (1005—015)
    - X-mas Card no. 16, 1989; (5 x 7) (1005—016)
    - X-mas Card no. 17, 1990; (5.75 x 8) (1005—017)
    - X-mas Card no. 18, 1991; (6 x 8) (1005—018)
    - X-mas Card no. 19, 1992; (5.75 x 8) (1005—019)
    - X-mas Card no. 20, 1993; (5.75 x 7.5) (1005—020)
    - X-mas Card no. 21, 1994; (5.5 x 8.25) (1005—021)
    - X-mas Card no. 22, 1995; (5.25 x 8) (1005—022)
    - X-mas Card no. 23, 1996; (5 x 7) (1005—023)
    - X-mas Card no. 24, 1997; (5 x 7) (1005—024)
    - X-mas Card no. 25, 1998; (5 x 7.5) (1005—025)
    - X-mas Card no. 26, 1999; (5.5 x 8) (1005—026)
    - X-mas Card no. 27, 2000; (8 x 10) (1005—027)
    - X-mas Card no. 28, 2001; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—028)
    - X-mas Card no. 29, 2002; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—029)
    - X-mas Card no. 30, 2003; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—030)
    - X-mas Card no. 31, 2004; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—031)
    - X-mas Card no. 32, 2005; (5 x 7) (1005—032)
    - X-mas Card no. 33, 2006; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—033)
    - X-mas Card no. 34, 2007; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—034)
    - X-mas Card no. 35, 2008; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—035)
    - X-mas Card no. 36, 2009; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—036)
    - X-mas Card no. 37, 2010; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—037)
    - X-mas Card no. 38, 2011; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—038)
    - X-mas Card no. 39, 2012; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—039)
    - X-mas Card no. 40, 2013; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—040)
    - X-mas Card no. 41, 2014; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—041)
    - X-mas Card no. 42, 2015; (5.5 x 7.5) (1005—042)
  - 1006: Early Seasons Greetings and Experiments
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1956; (9.5 x 5) (1006—001)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1957; (9 x 4.5) (1006—002)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1958; (8.25 x 8.25) (1006—003)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1959; (12 x 5.5) (1006—004)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1960; (13 x 4) (1006—005)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1961; (4.75 x 19) (1006—006)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1962; (4 x 9 folded) (1006—007)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1963; (19.5 x 9) (1006—008)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1964; (13 x 3.5) (1006—009)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1965; (11.5 x 7) (1006—010)
    - Early Seasons Greetings, 1966; (13 x 4) (1006—011)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1985; (5.25 x 7.5) (1006—012)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1988; (5 x 7) (1006—013)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1988; (5 x 7) (1006—014)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1990; (5.5 x 8) (1006—015)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1990; (5.5 x 8) (1006—016)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1991; (5.5 x 6.5) (1006—017)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1991; (5.5 x 6.5) (1006—018)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1991; (5.25 x 7) (1006—019)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1992; (5.5 x 8) (1006—020)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1992; (5.5 x 8) (1006—021)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1992; (5.75 x 8.25) (1006—022)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1993; (5.75 x 8) (1006—023)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1993; (5.5 x 6) (1006—024)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1993; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—025)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1994; (5.5 x 8.25) (1006—026)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 1998; (5.25 x 7) (1006—027)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2001; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—028)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2003; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—029)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2004; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—030)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2004; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—031)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2004; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—032)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2005; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—033)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2005; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—034)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2005; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—035)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2009; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—036)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2009; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—037)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2010; (5 x 6.5) (1006—038)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2010; (5 x 6.75) (1006—039)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2011; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—040)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2011; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—041)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2011; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—042)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2011; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—043)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2012; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—044)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2012; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—045)
    - X-mas Card Studies, 2013; (5.5 x 7.5) (1006—046)
- 2000 DRAWINGS
  - 2001: Drawings
    - Shack in Vermont – pencil drawing, 1961; (11 x 8) (2001—001)
    - Shack in Vermont – charcoal, 1961; (16.50 x 11.25) (2001—002)
    - Apartment in Lunenburg – charcoal, 1961; (16.50 x 11.25) (2001—003)
    - Apartment in Lunenburg – pencil, 1961; (11.25 x 16.50) (2001—004)
    - Apartment in Lunenburg – pencil, 1961; (11 .25 x 16.50) (2001—005)
    - Apt. in Brooklyn – pencil, 1962; (8 x 11) (2001—006)
    - Watertowers in Brooklyn – charcoal, 1962; (16.50 x 11.25) (2001—007)
    - Rooftop in Brooklyn – wax crayon, 1962; (16.50 x 11.25) (2001—008)
    - Blue Inspiration – wax crayon, 1962; (16.50 x 11.25) (2001—009)
    - Transformation – image transfer, pencil, 1968; (21.75 x 14) (2001—010)
    - Probability – pencil drawing, 1969; (25.50 x 18.50) (2001—011)
    - Tingle- pencil drawing + color markers, 1969; (17.75 x 18.25) (2001—012)
    - Vivacious – pencil over printed color field, 1969; (20 x 23.50) (2001—013)
    - Max – pencil over printed color field, 1969; (20.50 x 24) (2001—014)
    - Untitled – pencil over printed lines, 1970; (28 x 20) (2001—015)
    - Merry-Go-Round – pencil drawing and collage, 1973; (22 x 30) (2001—016)
    - Untitled – pencil and Acrylic - shaped, 1976; (13 x 14.50) (2001—017)
    - Untitled – gouache and acrylic, 1976; (15 x 14.50) (2001—018)
    - Untitled – drawing study for orbital piece, 1976; (13.50 x 15) (2001—019)
    - 22 part construction drawing for Wheels no. 2, 1982; (17 x 22) (2001—020)
    - Happy 60th Birthday – pencil drawing, 1989; (11 x 15) (2001—021)
    - Untitled – gouache, 1992; (18 x 9.50) (2001—022)
    - Untitled – gouache, 1992; (18 x 9.50) (2001—023)
    - Untitled – gouache, 1992; (18 x 9.50) (2001—024)
  - 2002: Sketchbooks
    - Sketchbook no. 1, 1965-1971; (8.5 x 11) (2002—001)
    - Sketchbook no. 2, 1972-1977; (11 x 14) (2002—002)
    - Sketchbook no. 3, 1977-1979; (8.5 x 11) (2002—003)
    - Sketchbook no. 4, 1979-1981; (8.5 x 11) (2002—004)
    - Sketchbook no. 5, 1981-1982; (8.5 x 11) (2002—005)
    - Sketchbook no. 6, 1982-1993; (8.5 x 11) (2002—006)
    - Sketchbook no. 7, 1982-1984; (11 x 14) (2002—007)
    - Sketchbook no. 8, 1984-1986; (11 x 14) (2002—008)
    - Sketchbook no. 9, 1988-1983; (8.5 x 11) (2002—009)
    - Sketchbook no. 10, 1990-2005; (11 x 14) (2002—010)
  - 2003: Scroll Drawings
    - 90 drawings on tissue, 1974; (40 x 30) (2003—001)
  - 2004: Doodles, Sketches and Studies
    - doodles, 1959; (4 x 4) (2004—001)
    - doodles, 1959; (2.25 x 4) (2004—002)
    - doodles, 1959; (5.5 x 4) (2004—003)
    - doodles, 1959; (7 x 7) (2004—004)
    - doodles, 1959; (5 x 8) (2004—005)
    - doodles, 1960; (5 x 5.5) (2004—006)
    - studies for painting, 1961; (4 x 6) (2004—007)
    - study for painting, 1962; (7 x 6) (2004—008)
    - sketch, 1962; (4 x 7.5) (2004—009)
    - doodle, 1963; (4.5 x 5.75) (2004—010)
    - doodle, 1963; (4.5 x 4.5) (2004—011)
    - doodles, 1964; (3 x 4) (2004—012)
    - doodle, 1964; (9.5 x 3.75) (2004—013)
    - doodle, 1964; (2.5 x 2.5) (2004—014)
    - doodle sketches, 1965; (9.75 x 8) (2004—015)
    - doodle sketches, 1965; (9.75 x 8) (2004—016)
    - doodle, 1968; (7.5 x 7.5) (2004—017)
    - doodle, 1968; (5 x 5.5) (2004—018)
    - doodle, 1968; (6.5 x 6.5) (2004—019)
    - doodle, 1968; (5.5 x 7.5) (2004—020)
    - doodle, 1968; (7.5 x7.5) (2004—021)
    - doodle, 1968; (3.75 x 3.5) (2004—022)
    - doodle sketch, 1968; (6 x 7) (2004—023)
    - doodle – Moon landing, 1968; (5 x 4) (2004—024)
    - sketch – Perky, 1969; (6.5 x 9) (2004—025)
    - doodle, 1971; (4 x 5.25) (2004—026)
    - doodle sketch, 1971; (10 x 8) (2004—027)
    - doodle sketch, 1971; (7.75 x 8.5) (2004—028)
    - doodle sketch, 1971; (8 x 10) (2004—029)
    - doodle sketch, 1971; (8 x 10) (2004—030)
    - doodle sketch, 1971; (8 x 10) (2004—031)
    - doodle sketch, 1971; (8 x 9) (2004—032)
    - doodle sketch, 1971; (8 x 10) (2004—033)
    - pencil drawing, 1975; (8 x 10) (2004—034)
    - doodle, 1976; (10 x 7.25) (2004—035)
    - study for a rug, 1976; (6 x 6) (2004—036)
    - study for a rug – Moon Ferry, 1976; (8 x 5) (2004—037)
    - study for a rug, 1976; (4 x 8.75) (2004—038)
    - doodle, 1977; (6.5 x 4.5) (2004—039)
    - study for a rug, 1977; (4 x 6.5) (2004—040)
    - study for a banner, 1977; (6 x 9.75) (2004—041)
    - study for wall painting, 1978; (10 x 8) (2004—042)
    - sketch for sculpture, 1978; (8 x 10) (2004—043)
    - study for sculpture on tissue, 1979; (6 x 8) (2004—044)
    - study for sculpture on tissue, 1979; (10 x 8) (2004—045)
    - study for sculpture on tissue, 1979; (8 x 8) (2004—046)
    - study for sculpture on tissue, 1979; (8 x 10) (2004—047)
    - doodle sketch, 1980; (7 dia.) (2004—048)
    - study for wall piece on tissue, 1981; (18.5 x 8) (2004—049)
    - study for wall piece on tissue, 1981; (17 x 5) (2004—050)
    - study for wall piece on tissue, 1981; (20 x 7) (2004—051)
    - study for sculpture group on tissue, 1981; (18 x 6) (2004—052)
    - doodle sketch for sculpture group, 1981; (7.5 x 6.5) (2004—053)
    - doodle sketches, 1981; (8 x 10) (2004—054)
    - study for ceiling piece, 1981; (10 x 8) (2004—055)
    - study for sculpture, 1981; (10 x 8) (2004—056)
    - study for wall piece on tissue, 1981; (16 x 8) (2004—057)
    - study for 4 story carpet on tissue, 1981; (8.5 x 24) (2004—058)
    - sketch for fountain on tissue, 1981; (10 x 8) (2004—059)
    - study for fountain on tissue, 1981; (10 x 6.5) (2004—060)
    - study for 4 story 'Zipper'on tissue, 1981; (6 x 9.5) (2004—061)
    - study for sculpture on tissue, 1981; (6 x 9) (2004—062)
    - sketch for sculpture, 1980; (12.5 x 10) (2004—063)
    - sketch for sculpture, 1983; (10 x 8) (2004—064)
    - sketch for sculpture, 1983; (8 x 8) (2004—065)
    - sketch for sculpture, 1983; (10 x 8) (2004—066)
    - sketch for sculpture, 1983; (10 x 8) (2004—067)
    - sketch for sculpture, 'Crisscross', 1984; (10 x 8) (2004—068)
    - study for rug on tissue, 1985; (9 .25 x 8) (2004—069)
    - sketches for wall piece, 1986; (8 x 10) (2004—070)
    - sketch for wall piece, 1986; (8 x 10) (2004—071)
    - sketch for wall piece, 1986; (8 x 10) (2004—072)
    - sketch for sculpture, 1987; (9.5 x 7.5) (2004—073)
    - studies for rug, 1989; (10 x 8) (2004—074)
    - study for rug, 1989; (10 x 8) (2004—075)
    - study for rug, 1989; (10 x 8) (2004—076)
    - study for rug, 1989; (10 x 8) (2004—077)
    - final sketch for rug, 1989; (10 x 8) (2004—078)
    - doodles, 1989; (9.5 x 4) (2004—079)
    - study for sculpture, 1998; (8 x 10) (2004—080)
    - sketch for scupture detail, 1998; (8 x 10) (2004—081)
    - sketches on the road – Italy, 1998; (7.5 x 7.75) (2004—082)
    - drawing, pencil and colored markers, 1969; (8.5 x 6.75) (2004—083)
    - sketch, colored pencils, 1974; (7.5 x 10) (2004—084)
    - sketch, sculpture installation, 1978; (8.5 x 10) (2004—085)
    - sketch for rug, 1979; (4.5 x 5.75) (2004—086)
    - acrylic and pencil, 1979; (6.5 x 10) (2004—087)
    - pencil and black marker drawing, 1980; (8 x 10) (2004—088)
    - pencil sketch, 1980; (8 x 9.5) (2004—089)
    - pencil sketch, 1980; (8 x 10) (2004—090)
    - hand colored xerox print, 1980; (8 x 10) (2004—091)
    - pencil sketch, 1980; (8 x 10) (2004—092)
    - design for rug, 1982; (8.75 x 6.25) (2004—093)
    - design for banner, 1984; (5.75 x 8.75) (2004—094)
    - first sketches for Brusberg flags, 1984; (10 x 8) (2004—095)
  - 2005: Banana Drawings
    - Electric Banana no. 4, 1974; (print and drawing, 40 x 30) (2005—001)
    - Do-It-Yourself Banana Kit no. 6, 1976; (print and drawing, 40 x 30) (2005—002)
    - Split Banana no. 7, 1976; (print and drawing, 40 x 30) (2005—003)
    - Two-Way Banana no. 7, 1976; (print and drawing, 40 x 30) (2005—004)
    - Poartable Banana no. 7, 1976; (print and drawing, 40 x 30) (2005—005)
    - Banana Coupe no. 7, 1976; (print and drawing, 30 x 40) (2005—006)
    - Split Banana no. 7, 1979; (print and drawing, 40 x 30) (2005—007)
- 3000 PRINTS
  - 3001: Drawings and Sketches of Prints
    - Collage, 1971; (8.5 x 11) (3001—001)
    - Black and White Tracing, 1972; (6.5 x 7) (3001—002)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1974; (5.5 x 7) (3001—003)
    - Color Drawing, 1974; (8.5 x 11) (3001—004)
    - Color Drawing, 1974; (6.75 x 9.5) (3001—005)
    - Collage / Drawing, 1975; (4.5 x 6 ) (3001—006)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—007)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (6.5 x 8.25) (3001—008)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (6 x 4.25) (3001—009)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (6.5 x 5.75) (3001—010)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (5.5 x 4.5) (3001—011)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (5.75 x 3.75) (3001—012)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (6.75 x 5) (3001—013)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—014)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (7 x 9) (3001—015)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (5.25 x 6.5) (3001—016)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (5 x 7) (3001—017)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (5.25 x 7.5) (3001—018)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (5.75 x 7.5) (3001—019)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (7.75 x 4.5) (3001—020)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (7.25 x 5.25) (3001—021)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (7.25 x 5) (3001—022)
    - Color Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 5.25) (3001—023)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (3.5 x 5.5) (3001—024)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—025)
    - Black and White Sketches, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—026)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—027)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—028)
    - Black and White Sketches, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—029)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—030)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (5 x 6.25) (3001—031)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (4.25 x 5.5) (3001—032)
    - Black and White Sketches, 1975; (11 x 0.5) (3001—033)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (11 x 0.5) (3001—034)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (11 x 0.5) (3001—035)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—036)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—037)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (5.25 x 6.5) (3001—038)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (5.75 x 7.5) (3001—039)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (5 x 6.25) (3001—040)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—041)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—042)
    - Black and White Studies, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—043)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—044)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—045)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—046)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—047)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (8.5 x 6.25) (3001—048)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (6.5 x 4.75) (3001—049)
    - Black and White Study, 1975; (3.75 x 5) (3001—050)
    - Black and White Study, 1975; (4 x 5) (3001—051)
    - Black and White Study, 1975; (4.75 x 5) (3001—052)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (6.5 x 8.25) (3001—053)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (6.5 x 9) (3001—054)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (6.75 x 9) (3001—055)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (6 x 7.5) (3001—056)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (7.25 x 9) (3001—057)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (6 x 7.5) (3001—058)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (6.75 x 6.25) (3001—059)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (7 x 8.5) (3001—060)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (6 x 8) (3001—061)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (5.5 x 7.25) (3001—062)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (6 x 7.5) (3001—063)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (4 x 5.25) (3001—064)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—065)
    - Black and White Studies, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—066)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—067)
    - Black and White Studies, 1975; (8.5 x 11) (3001—068)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—069)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—070)
    - Color Drawing, 1975; (9 x 6.5) (3001—071)
    - Black and White Study, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—072)
    - Black and White Study, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—073)
    - Black and White Study, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—074)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—075)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—076)
    - Black and White Studies, 1975; (11 x 8.5) (3001—077)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (6.5 x 8.5) (3001—078)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1976; (5.25 x 6.25) (3001—079)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (3.75 x 0.25) (3001—080)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (4.5 x 5.25) (3001—081)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1976; (6.25 x 6.75) (3001—082)
    - Black and White Studies, 1976; (7.25 x 6) (3001—083)
    - Color Study, 1976; (5.75 x 7) (3001—084)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (7 x 5.5) (3001—085)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (7 x 5.25) (3001—086)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (6 x 8.25) (3001—087)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (8.25 x 8) (3001—088)
    - Color Study, 1976; (11 x 8.5) (3001—089)
    - Color Study, 1976; (4.75 x 5.5) (3001—090)
    - Color Study, 1976; (8.5 x 11) (3001—091)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (8.5 x 11) (3001—092)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (8.5 x 11) (3001—093)
    - Color Study, 1976; (11 x 8.5) (3001—094)
    - Color Study, 1976; (11 x 8.5) (3001—095)
    - Color Study, 1976; (8.5 x 11) (3001—096)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (8.5 x 11) (3001—097)
    - Color Studies, 1976; (11 x 8.5) (3001—098)
    - Color Studies, 1976; (11 x 8.5) (3001—099)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (8.5 x 11) (3001—100)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (8.25 x 6.5) (3001—101)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (7 x 5) (3001—102)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (4 x 9) (3001—103)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (8.5 x 11) (3001—104)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (5 x 7) (3001—105)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (4 x 6.5) (3001—106)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (5 x 7.5) (3001—107)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (6.5 x 7.75) (3001—108)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (3.5 x 4.75) (3001—109)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (6 x 7.5) (3001—110)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (6.5 x 7.5) (3001—111)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (5.75 x 9.25) (3001—112)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (6.25 x 7.5) (3001—113)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (7.75 x 9.25) (3001—114)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (6.5 x 7.5) (3001—115)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (5.25 x 8.5) (3001—116)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (8.5 x 11) (3001—117)
    - Black and White Study, 1976; (5 x 6) (3001—118)
    - Black and White Study, 1976; (4.75 x 6.5) (3001—119)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (4.5 x 5.75) (3001—120)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (5 x 6) (3001—121)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (5.5 x 8) (3001—122)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (6.5 X 6.5) (3001—123)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (5 x 6.25) (3001—124)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (5.25 x 5.75) (3001—125)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (5.5 x 6) (3001—126)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1976; (5.5 x 9) (3001—127)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (7.5 x 10) (3001—128)
    - Color Drawing, 1976; (8.5 x 11) (3001—129)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (6.5 x 8.75) (3001—130)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (5.5 x 8.25) (3001—131)
    - Color Sketch, 1976; (7.75 x 6.5) (3001—132)
    - Color Drawing, 1977; (3.75 x 5.25) (3001—133)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1977; (4.25 x 5.75) (3001—134)
    - Color Drawing, 1977; (4.25 x 6) (3001—135)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1977; (4.25 x 6) (3001—136)
    - Collage, 1970; (9.5 x 15) (3001—137)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1971; (5.25 x 6.25) (3001—138)
    - B. P. P. Drawing, 1971; (8 x 10.5) (3001—139)
    - B. P. P. Drawing, 1971; (8 x 10.5) (3001—140)
    - B. P. P. Drawing, 1971; (8 x 10.5) (3001—141)
    - B. P. P. Drawing, 1971; (8 x 10.5) (3001—142)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (8.75 x 12.5) (3001—143)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (8.75 x 12.5) (3001—144)
    - Color Drawing, 1972; (8.75 x 12.5) (3001—145)
    - Color Drawing, 1972; (8.75 x 12.5) (3001—146)
    - Color Drawing, 1972; (8.75 x 12.5) (3001—147)
    - Color Drawing, 1972; (8.75 x 12.5) (3001—148)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (8.75 x 12.5) (3001—149)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (8.75 x 12.5) (3001—150)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (7 x 11) (3001—151)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (7 x 11) (3001—152)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (7 x 11) (3001—153)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (7 x 11) (3001—154)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (7 x 11) (3001—155)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (7 x 10) (3001—156)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (7 x 10) (3001—157)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1972; (7 x 10) (3001—158)
    - Color Drawing, 1973; (7 x 10) (3001—159)
    - Color Drawing, 1973; (7 x 10) (3001—160)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1973; (8.75 x 12.5) (3001—161)
    - Color Drawing, 1973; (6.25 x 8.5) (3001—162)
    - Color Sketch, 1973; (6.5 x 7) (3001—163)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1973; (8 x 12) (3001—164)
    - Color Sketch, 1973; (8 x 12) (3001—165)
    - Color Sketch, 1973; (4.25 x 6.5) (3001—166)
    - Color Sketch, 1973; (6.75 x 9) (3001—167)
    - Color Sketch, 1973; (8 x 9) (3001—168)
    - Color Sketch, 1973; (6.5 diameter) (3001—169)
    - Color Drawing, 1973; (7.75 x 10) (3001—170)
    - Color Drawing, 1973; (8.75 x 11.25) (3001—171)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (7 x 7) (3001—172)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—173)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—174)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—175)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—176)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—177)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—178)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—179)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—180)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—181)
    - Color Drawing, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—182)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—183)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—184)
    - Color Drawing, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—185)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8 x 10.5) (3001—186)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—187)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—188)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—189)
    - Color Drawing, 1974; (8 x 10.5) (3001—190)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—191)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—192)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—193)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—194)
    - Blue Marker Drawing, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—195)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 9.5) (3001—196)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—197)
    - Black and White Drawings, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—198)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—199)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—200)
    - Black and White Drawings, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—201)
    - Black Marker Drawing, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—202)
    - Blue Marker Drawing, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—203)
    - Black and White Sketches, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—204)
    - Black and White Sketches, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—205)
    - Black and White Sketches, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—206)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 13 .75) (folded) (3001—207)
    - Black and White Sketches, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (both sides) (3001—208)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—209)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—210)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—211)
    - Color Sketches, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—212)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (6.5 x 9.75) (3001—213)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—214)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—215)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—216)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—217)